<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>José Coelho</title>
      <link>https://jose.co.nz</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on José Coelho</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>Building this website</title>
    <link>https://jose.co.nz/Software-Engineer/Building-this-website</link>
    <guid>https://jose.co.nz/Software-Engineer/Building-this-website</guid>
    <description>I use Obsidian to take notes, and I’ve been taking notes for quite a while. I thought on sharing more of my projects and decided to grab some of my notes and publish it.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 10:13:09 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Make it work, then make it better</title>
    <link>https://jose.co.nz/Software-Engineer/Make-it-work,-then-make-it-better</link>
    <guid>https://jose.co.nz/Software-Engineer/Make-it-work,-then-make-it-better</guid>
    <description>To avoid Paralysis Analysis, what helps me move along is do it dirty first, make it work, learn as much as you can at this stage, then commit to an idea ...</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 08:20:27 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>José Coelho</title>
    <link>https://jose.co.nz/</link>
    <guid>https://jose.co.nz/</guid>
    <description>Hello I’m José Coelho, I’m a father, husband and my passion is tinkering and learning. My professional mission is to bring joy to the ones around me while delivering value.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 08:18:07 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>When stuck, ask for help ASAP</title>
    <link>https://jose.co.nz/Software-Engineer/When-stuck,-ask-for-help-ASAP</link>
    <guid>https://jose.co.nz/Software-Engineer/When-stuck,-ask-for-help-ASAP</guid>
    <description>When stuck, ask for help ASAP If you get stuck in to a problem, ask for help as soon as possible. As a rule of thumb, 30 minutes is good, more than 1 hour is probably to long.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 21:21:32 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Your method is telling a story</title>
    <link>https://jose.co.nz/Software-Engineer/Your-method-is-telling-a-story</link>
    <guid>https://jose.co.nz/Software-Engineer/Your-method-is-telling-a-story</guid>
    <description>Write your methods in way that is easy to understand what is their purpose, and what you are trying to achieve with that. add examples This is part of Tips for Software Engineers.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 20:21:32 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Vertical Slicing</title>
    <link>https://jose.co.nz/Software-Engineer/Vertical-Slicing</link>
    <guid>https://jose.co.nz/Software-Engineer/Vertical-Slicing</guid>
    <description>Let’s start with some Principles behind the Agile Manifesto: Our highest priority is to satisfy the customer through early and continuous delivery of valuable software ...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 20:21:32 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Write it down to solve it</title>
    <link>https://jose.co.nz/Zettelkasten/Write-it-down-to-solve-it</link>
    <guid>https://jose.co.nz/Zettelkasten/Write-it-down-to-solve-it</guid>
    <description>Write it down to organise your ideas When I write something down, it is easier to organize my mind and make things clear. I tend to run in circles, until I start writing it down.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:32:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Approach with curiosity</title>
    <link>https://jose.co.nz/Software-Engineer/Approach-with-curiosity</link>
    <guid>https://jose.co.nz/Software-Engineer/Approach-with-curiosity</guid>
    <description>When someone does something in a way that you do not agree, approach with curiosity, you may be able to learn something today! ask why things are done in certain way 3 questions, then ...</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 23:23:40 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Build trust by communicating often</title>
    <link>https://jose.co.nz/Contexts/Paloma/Build-trust-by-communicating-often</link>
    <guid>https://jose.co.nz/Contexts/Paloma/Build-trust-by-communicating-often</guid>
    <description>prensentation The problem: You are craving for a bagel from the airport and decide to hire someone to bring that to you. The solution: Hire a driver to deliver this package We hire someone The driver comes, they charge $100 per hour and estimates that it will take 1 hour to pick this package up, but it could take longer.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 03:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Atomic Habits</title>
    <link>https://jose.co.nz/Books/Atomic-Habits</link>
    <guid>https://jose.co.nz/Books/Atomic-Habits</guid>
    <description>I’ve listen to it using Audible. Liked it, but didn’t put much in practice… 😬 Well, if I have to choose, these are the main bits that I tend to remind myself New habits must be easy, like leave your running clothes ready or try 2 minutes of exercise I did try multiple times, but still missing more commitment.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 23:24:53 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>